<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>web - Tag - CUEH ComSec</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/tags/web/</link><description>web - Tag - CUEH ComSec</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 12:40:28 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cov-comsec.github.io/tags/web/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>SQL Injection</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2021_sqli/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2022 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2021_sqli/</guid><description>SQL Injection Further on today, we will be using THM If you haven&amp;rsquo;t registered go to tryhackme.com Ensure you have the VPN file or AttackBox ready SQL Structured Query Language (SQL) is used to communicate with databases and has the capability to delete, edit, insert or retrieve data. There are a few variations of SQL which have some slight syntactical differences. A few examples are MySQL, SQL Server and SQLite.</description></item><item><title>Exploiting Race Conditions</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2022_race_conditions/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2022 08:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2022_race_conditions/</guid><description>During this session we discussed the concept of race conditions in various forms, and how an attacker could exploit them. To recap, as race condition takes advantage of the fact that a system must execute a process in a specific sequence of steps, but due to the nature of modern systems there is an opportunity to alter the environment in which a process in run during this sequence of events. One common form of race condition is a Time-of-Check, Time-of-Use vulnerability (TOCTOU).</description></item><item><title>Introduction, Recon &amp; OSINT Taster Session</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2021_taster_session/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 20:14:41 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2021_taster_session/</guid><description>Welcome back to our first official session for the new academic year, it was great to finally meet you all in real life. This is a quick recap of what we did.
What is ComSec? Welcome to ComSec, we are Coventry University&amp;rsquo;s Ethical Hacking Society. We aim to share our knowledge around cybersecurity and to create a strong info-sec community. Our aims:
Teach cybersecurity Organise talks with businesses Organise university wide competitions Compete internationally with our team ‘Ethical Slackers Committee 2021 This year the committee is:</description></item><item><title>CUEHack</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/cuehack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/cuehack/</guid><description>To end this academic year, ComSec helped second-year student Alex to run a CTF building inspired hackathon over the weekend of the 20th of March 2021.
The idea was simple, teams had to build a CTF challenge utilising a docker template that we created as a starting point. To find out more information click here.
Entries 1st Place Ben&amp;rsquo;s Team with Viral Breakout 2nd Place Richie&amp;rsquo;s Team</description></item><item><title>Web Exploitation &amp; OWASP</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/owasp_sqli_xss/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/owasp_sqli_xss/</guid><description>This week we will begin to look at website exploitation, using the OWASP top 10. The main areas we will cover are:
Good notes, and their importance Making notes with Markdown What is website exploitation? Introduction to OWASP top 10 SQL Injection Sqlmap Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Sensitive Data Exposure Resources Presentation Slides Note Taking Effective hacking requires a thorough and methodological approach. Additionally, in the workplace you will have to report findings to clients and be able to work with others.</description></item></channel></rss>