<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Web Shells - Tag - CUEH ComSec</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/tags/web-shells/</link><description>Web Shells - Tag - CUEH ComSec</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 20:14:41 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cov-comsec.github.io/tags/web-shells/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction, Recon &amp; OSINT Taster Session</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2021_taster_session/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 20:14:41 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2021_taster_session/</guid><description>Welcome back to our first official session for the new academic year, it was great to finally meet you all in real life. This is a quick recap of what we did.
What is ComSec? Welcome to ComSec, we are Coventry University&amp;rsquo;s Ethical Hacking Society. We aim to share our knowledge around cybersecurity and to create a strong info-sec community. Our aims:
Teach cybersecurity Organise talks with businesses Organise university wide competitions Compete internationally with our team ‘Ethical Slackers Committee 2021 This year the committee is:</description></item><item><title>Web Enumeration Writeup</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/web_enum_writeup/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/web_enum_writeup/</guid><description>Web Enumeration ctf Start your docker instances and let&amp;rsquo;s hack! 8 flags inside this machine
Every time first thing to do Nmap scan Look at your scan results. So we have one port open 3838/tcp and we have at least one directory &amp;lsquo;/legal&amp;rsquo; and one file robots.txt and the box is running nginx. First thing lets open the browser and navigate to 172.17.0.2 Get a good look at the source code and the style.</description></item><item><title>Web Enumeration</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/web_enum/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/web_enum/</guid><description>In this session, we will look at website enumeration and exploitation. This is what we will cover in further detail:
What is Enumeration? Directory Brute Forcing Checking Comments &amp;amp; Common Files Directory Traversal Google Dorking (basics) Server Fingerprinting &amp;amp; Other Tools Web Shells Resources Presentation Slides Live Session Recording What is Enumeration? Enumeration is the process of going through a list, one by one, to find information.</description></item></channel></rss>