<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Academic Year 2020-21 - Category - CUEH ComSec</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/categories/academic-year-2020-21/</link><description>Academic Year 2020-21 - Category - CUEH ComSec</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 12:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cov-comsec.github.io/categories/academic-year-2020-21/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Galactic CTF Announcement</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2022_galactic_announcement/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2022_galactic_announcement/</guid><description>&lt;p>Starting on the 9th of August 2022 at 12:00 UTC CUEH is proud to host the first internal Coventry University group CTF.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>CUEHack</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/cuehack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/cuehack/</guid><description>To end this academic year, ComSec helped second-year student Alex to run a CTF building inspired hackathon over the weekend of the 20th of March 2021.
The idea was simple, teams had to build a CTF challenge utilising a docker template that we created as a starting point. To find out more information click here.
Entries 1st Place Ben&amp;rsquo;s Team with Viral Breakout 2nd Place Richie&amp;rsquo;s Team</description></item><item><title>Nettitude Event</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/nettitude/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/nettitude/</guid><description>Today, we will have a talk from cybersecurity business Nettitude. Topics that will be covered will be what the industry is like and their graduate/internship schemes.
You will be able to talk to graduate students and their experiences, and the event will be rounded up with a CTF competition!
To find out more about Nettitude click here.</description></item><item><title>Bulletproof Event</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/bulletproof/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/bulletproof/</guid><description>Today, we will be having a talk by cybersecurity business Bulletproof.
The talk will include topics like what it is like to work in the security industry and the many different areas. Additionally, you will be able to talk to graduate students and have a chance to ask questions. Finally, the event will be capped off with a CTF!
We would like to thank Bulletproof for holding the event, click here to find more about them.</description></item><item><title>Bug Reporting &amp; Meterpreter</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/bugreporting_meterpreter/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/bugreporting_meterpreter/</guid><description>This week we will continue from the Metasploit session and explore Meterpreter, but firstly we will look at bug reporting.
Resources Presentation Slides Bug Reporting Due to the current working at home predicament, it can be hard for lecturers and us to debug issues. Unfortunately receiving messages containing &amp;lsquo;it doesn&amp;rsquo;t work&amp;rsquo; is unhelpful and time wasting. Therefore, in this session we will cover how to bug report.
Tip Remember, before asking for help to attempt to try and solve the problem yourself (such as reading documentation, trying our top 5 mistakes and Ducking for answers).</description></item><item><title>12 Days of Christmas CTF Review</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/12days_xmas_ctf_review/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/12days_xmas_ctf_review/</guid><description>This week we will discuss solutions to the 12 days of Christmas CTF that we created. Not had a go - look at CTFd to take part!
Before starting this week, we would like to announce the winners:
1st ¯_(ツ)_/¯ 3230pts 2nd NotSuspicious 1730pts 3rd Jeff 1040pts Best Write-up - Ben We would also like to thank everyone who took part, and we hoped that you enjoyed the challenges.</description></item><item><title>Metasploit</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/metasploit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/metasploit/</guid><description>Today, we will look at Metasploit; a widely used pen testing framework. Metasploit is a massive product and today we will focus on:
What is Metasploit? What is msfconsole? What is Metasploitable2? Using Nmap in msfconsole Running an exploit using Metasploit Resources Presentation Slides Tip In the examples, I run exploits against Metasploitable 2 (a deliberately vulnerable VM). You can download it here. What is Metasploit?</description></item><item><title>12 Days of Christmas CTF</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/12days_xmas_ctf/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/12days_xmas_ctf/</guid><description>Dear Loyal Subjects,
The Three Kings have received a prophecy about the birth of God&amp;rsquo;s son in twelve days’ time!
Unfortunately, King Herald has also heard this news and has ordered the death of all babies within his kingdom. Since King Herald has many spies, we have had to enclose hidden information within this letter.
Can you help the three Kings reach God&amp;rsquo;s son and ensure his safety? To do this, each day there will be three daily challenges to complete for the next 12 days (starting 26th December) with varying difficulties aimed at a range of abilities.</description></item><item><title>Guest - 0verfl0w_ - Banking Malware</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/bankingmalware_overfl0w/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/bankingmalware_overfl0w/</guid><description>This week we had a talk by a second-year student, 0verfl0w_ about banking malware and his experience while working as a Principal Security Analyst. Additionally, he has developed a Beginner Malware Analysis Course, Zero2Automated, and worked with SentinelOne to develop free online training courses.
Here is a copy of the presentation. If you have any questions, feel free to reach out to @0verfl0w_ on Twitter.</description></item><item><title>CrowdStrike Event</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/crowdstrike_event/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/crowdstrike_event/</guid><description>Our university has been hacked!!!! CrowdStrike and ComSec request your help in identifying the malicious attackers. Can you help us identify the attackers before Warwick, Southampton and Edinburgh Napier do?
This week we will complete a blue team, security operation centre type challenge!
Unfortunately, places are limited this week, and require booking in advance - to book, view our post on either Aula or Discord
Who are CrowdStrike? &amp;lsquo;CrowdStrike was founded in 2011 to fix a fundamental problem: The sophisticated attacks that were forcing the world’s leading businesses into the headlines could not be solved with existing malware-based defences.</description></item></channel></rss>