<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Academic Year 2021-22 - Category - CUEH ComSec</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/categories/academic-year-2021-22/</link><description>Academic Year 2021-22 - Category - CUEH ComSec</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 22:40:28 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cov-comsec.github.io/categories/academic-year-2021-22/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Week 2: Scanning and Enumeration</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/scanning/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 22:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/scanning/</guid><description>In this session we will begin to look at scanning and enummeration, and start to look at some of the associated tools.
Warm Up - Getting help in the Terminal Ever forgotten a command or switch in linux - here&amp;rsquo;s two great ways to find help; all from the comfort of your terminal!
&amp;ndash;help Virtually all commands in linux have built-in help, all you need to do is append --help to the end of your command.</description></item><item><title>Week 1: OSINT Chalange Writeup</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/week1_writeup/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/week1_writeup/</guid><description><![CDATA[Intro The first-week challenge covers the basics of OSINT research, opening remote connections and password cracking. I will try to cover most of the methods we can use to get through Jack&rsquo;s cat and Ben&rsquo;s secure passwords. Without further ado, let&rsquo;s begin.
Challenge 1: Web Username The first one was very tricky for me as I am not a cat person and don&rsquo;t enjoy cat pictures&hellip; Anyway, as we go to the landing page, we can see that there are home(1) and login(2) pages and some information(3) about some employees.]]></description></item><item><title>Week1: Intro, Recon &amp; OSINT</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/taster_week1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 20:14:41 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/taster_week1/</guid><description>Welcome back to our first official session for the new academic year, it was great to finally meet you all in real life. This is a quick recap of what we did.
What is ComSec? Welcome to ComSec, we are Coventry University&amp;rsquo;s Ethical Hacking Society. We aim to share our knowledge around cybersecurity and to create a strong info-sec community. Our aims:
Teach cybersecurity Organise talks with businesses Organise university wide competitions Compete internationally with our team ‘Ethical Slackers Committee 2021 This year the committee is:</description></item><item><title>We're Back!</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/welcome_2021/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/welcome_2021/</guid><description>Welcome to a new year at ComSec — Coventry University&amp;rsquo;s unofficial ethical hacking society. We are proud to announce due to the relaxation of COVID-19 rules, we will be holding in-person events every week on Wednesday at 2pm. Also, if the interest is there; we will offer a live-streamed version available on our Discord channel (please let the committee know prior to the session). We would also, like to take this opportunity to formally welcome our latest committee member, Ben!</description></item></channel></rss>