<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Nmap - Tag - CUEH ComSec</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/tags/nmap/</link><description>Nmap - Tag - CUEH ComSec</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 22:40:28 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cov-comsec.github.io/tags/nmap/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Week 2: Scanning and Enumeration</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/scanning/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 22:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/scanning/</guid><description>In this session we will begin to look at scanning and enummeration, and start to look at some of the associated tools.
Warm Up - Getting help in the Terminal Ever forgotten a command or switch in linux - here&amp;rsquo;s two great ways to find help; all from the comfort of your terminal!
&amp;ndash;help Virtually all commands in linux have built-in help, all you need to do is append --help to the end of your command.</description></item><item><title>Web Enumeration Writeup</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/web_enum_writeup/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/web_enum_writeup/</guid><description>Web Enumeration ctf Start your docker instances and let&amp;rsquo;s hack! 8 flags inside this machine
Every time first thing to do Nmap scan Look at your scan results. So we have one port open 3838/tcp and we have at least one directory &amp;lsquo;/legal&amp;rsquo; and one file robots.txt and the box is running nginx. First thing lets open the browser and navigate to 172.17.0.2 Get a good look at the source code and the style.</description></item><item><title>Web Enumeration</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/web_enum/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/web_enum/</guid><description>In this session, we will look at website enumeration and exploitation. This is what we will cover in further detail:
What is Enumeration? Directory Brute Forcing Checking Comments &amp;amp; Common Files Directory Traversal Google Dorking (basics) Server Fingerprinting &amp;amp; Other Tools Web Shells Resources Presentation Slides Live Session Recording What is Enumeration? Enumeration is the process of going through a list, one by one, to find information.</description></item><item><title>ComSec Introduction Writeup</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/welcome_nmap_writeup/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/welcome_nmap_writeup/</guid><description>Nmap 1 Welcome to ComSec&amp;rsquo;s first challenge! This week we will be targeting a docker container, to start it, issue the following two commands:
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 $ wget https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/welcome_nmap/c1/docker-compose.yaml $ sudo docker-compose up [sudo] password for kali: WARNING: Found orphan containers (kali_evilweb_1) for this project. If you removed or renamed this service in your compose file, you can run this command with the --remove-orphans flag to clean it up.</description></item><item><title>ComSec Introduction</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/welcome_nmap/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/welcome_nmap/</guid><description>This week is the first session of the academic year, and we will cover:
What is ComSec? Network Scanning with Nmap Introduction to TryHackMe Resources Presentation Slides Live Session Recording Docker-Compose Challenges Challenge 1 Challenge 2 What is ComSec? Firstly, welcome to ComSec, we are the university&amp;rsquo;s unofficial ethical hacking society. This year the club will be led by second year students Jack Orcherton, Martin Schon and Tiago Pascoal.</description></item></channel></rss>