<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Docker - Tag - CUEH ComSec</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/tags/docker/</link><description>Docker - Tag - CUEH ComSec</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 12:40:28 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cov-comsec.github.io/tags/docker/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Assembly &amp; Shellcoding</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2021_assembly_and_shellcoding/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2021_assembly_and_shellcoding/</guid><description>This week Ben led a session on some basic assembly shellcoding. The first section of the session covered some foundational theory content on CPU architecture, registers, and memory. After this, assembly was introduced - we used x86_64 assembly with Intel syntax. In this article we will go through one method of solving each assembly challenge. The shellcode solutions will be released at a later date.
You can download the presentation here.</description></item><item><title>Scanning and Enumeration</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2021_scanning/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 22:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2021_scanning/</guid><description>In this session we will begin to look at scanning and enummeration, and start to look at some of the associated tools.
Warm Up - Getting help in the Terminal Ever forgotten a command or switch in linux - here&amp;rsquo;s two great ways to find help; all from the comfort of your terminal!
&amp;ndash;help Virtually all commands in linux have built-in help, all you need to do is append --help to the end of your command.</description></item><item><title>CUEHack</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/cuehack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/cuehack/</guid><description>To end this academic year, ComSec helped second-year student Alex to run a CTF building inspired hackathon over the weekend of the 20th of March 2021.
The idea was simple, teams had to build a CTF challenge utilising a docker template that we created as a starting point. To find out more information click here.
Entries 1st Place Ben&amp;rsquo;s Team with Viral Breakout 2nd Place Richie&amp;rsquo;s Team</description></item><item><title>How-To: docker-compose</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/docker-compose/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/docker-compose/</guid><description>This year we will be using a lot of docker machines. They are like virtual machines, however slimed down, therefore using less resources and have smaller file sizes. We recommend running docker on your Kali Linux machine (or Debian based distribution), even though it can run on Windows, it can be temperamental at times. Therefore, this is a guide for Linux only.
Installation Firstly, ensure your system is fully up to date, then install the necessary packages.</description></item></channel></rss>