<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>guest - Tag - CUEH ComSec</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/tags/guest/</link><description>guest - Tag - CUEH ComSec</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 12:40:28 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cov-comsec.github.io/tags/guest/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Nettitude Event</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/nettitude/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/nettitude/</guid><description>Today, we will have a talk from cybersecurity business Nettitude. Topics that will be covered will be what the industry is like and their graduate/internship schemes.
You will be able to talk to graduate students and their experiences, and the event will be rounded up with a CTF competition!
To find out more about Nettitude click here.</description></item><item><title>Bulletproof Event</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/bulletproof/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/bulletproof/</guid><description>Today, we will be having a talk by cybersecurity business Bulletproof.
The talk will include topics like what it is like to work in the security industry and the many different areas. Additionally, you will be able to talk to graduate students and have a chance to ask questions. Finally, the event will be capped off with a CTF!
We would like to thank Bulletproof for holding the event, click here to find more about them.</description></item><item><title>Guest - 0verfl0w_ - Banking Malware</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/bankingmalware_overfl0w/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/bankingmalware_overfl0w/</guid><description>This week we had a talk by a second-year student, 0verfl0w_ about banking malware and his experience while working as a Principal Security Analyst. Additionally, he has developed a Beginner Malware Analysis Course, Zero2Automated, and worked with SentinelOne to develop free online training courses.
Here is a copy of the presentation. If you have any questions, feel free to reach out to @0verfl0w_ on Twitter.</description></item><item><title>CrowdStrike Event</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/crowdstrike_event/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/crowdstrike_event/</guid><description>Our university has been hacked!!!! CrowdStrike and ComSec request your help in identifying the malicious attackers. Can you help us identify the attackers before Warwick, Southampton and Edinburgh Napier do?
This week we will complete a blue team, security operation centre type challenge!
Unfortunately, places are limited this week, and require booking in advance - to book, view our post on either Aula or Discord
Who are CrowdStrike? &amp;lsquo;CrowdStrike was founded in 2011 to fix a fundamental problem: The sophisticated attacks that were forcing the world’s leading businesses into the headlines could not be solved with existing malware-based defences.</description></item><item><title>Guest - ROP Chains</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/sleepunderflow_rop/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/sleepunderflow_rop/</guid><description>This week, we had a talk by graduate student and security consultant at Nettitude, Sleepunderflow! To view the materials he used, head to his GitHub Repo
Resources Presentation Slides Live Session Recording</description></item><item><title>Guest Lecturer - Buffer Overflows</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/dan_buffer_overflow/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/dan_buffer_overflow/</guid><description>This week we had a guest lecture by Dan, a senior lecturer at Coventry University. To view his materials and challenges, please visit Coventry University GitHub.</description></item></channel></rss>