<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>All Posts - CUEH ComSec</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/</link><description>All Posts | CUEH ComSec</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 12:40:28 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Twelvetide CTF</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2021_twelvetide/</link><pubDate>Tue, 14 Dec 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2021_twelvetide/</guid><description>Hi everyone,
Hope you&amp;rsquo;re all enjoying yourselves now that coursework deadlines have passed. As Christmas approaches ComSec would like to announce the dates of our Christmas CTF - Twelvetide.
The CTF will last 15 days, with new challenges released every day for the first 12 days. Difficulty will range from entry-level to intermediate, so make sure you sign on and give it a go!
More details will be released on the ComSec discord in coming days.</description></item><item><title>Walkthrough: Shellcoding Challenges</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2021_assembly_and_shellcoding_walkthrough/</link><pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 10:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2021_assembly_and_shellcoding_walkthrough/</guid><description>As promised by Ben in Assembly &amp;amp; Shellcoding, this article will cover the solutions for the Shellcode challenges. The challenges can be found on CTFd and is strongly recommended to try to solve the challenges on your own before continue reading this article!
Preparation for the challenges Each of the following challenges will require you to send your already assembled code to the target; whose ip address and port is specified in the description of each challenge on CTFd.</description></item><item><title>Introduction to Stack Smashing</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2021_stack_smashing/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Nov 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2021_stack_smashing/</guid><description>This week, Ben introduced the concept of stack smashing, demonstrating the most basic form of buffer overflow attacks, the stack smash.
Presentation slides here
The term stack smashing was first coined in the Phrack article Smashing the Stack for Fun and Profit. It is a term used to describe the technique of overflowing a buffer, writing shellcode onto the stack (and sometimes a NOP sled), and then overwriting the return address of a the stack frame with the address near the start of the payload.</description></item><item><title>Reverse Engineering Basics</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2021_reverse_engineering/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2021_reverse_engineering/</guid><description>The session at ComSec this week went into some basic reverse engineering methods. Ben did a demo with some challenges, and then we released some CTF challenges to solve.
Credential Leak via Memory Inspection The first demo showed how we can use a decompiler to understand how a binary functions, and then use a debugger to inspect memory at runtime in order to find credentials. You can download the demo binary here.</description></item><item><title>Assembly &amp; Shellcoding</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2021_assembly_and_shellcoding/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2021_assembly_and_shellcoding/</guid><description>This week Ben led a session on some basic assembly shellcoding. The first section of the session covered some foundational theory content on CPU architecture, registers, and memory. After this, assembly was introduced - we used x86_64 assembly with Intel syntax. In this article we will go through one method of solving each assembly challenge. The shellcode solutions will be released at a later date.
You can download the presentation here.</description></item><item><title>Octalkber</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/octalkber/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/octalkber/</guid><description>Throughout the month of October, for cybersecurity awareness month, each week we will be having a talk by someone in the cybersecurity field. To see our latest line-up and how to gain access to these talks; please refer to the posts in Aula and the ComSec Discord channel.
Thanks,
ComSec</description></item><item><title>Scanning and Enumeration</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2021_scanning/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 22:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2021_scanning/</guid><description>In this session we will begin to look at scanning and enummeration, and start to look at some of the associated tools.
Warm Up - Getting help in the Terminal Ever forgotten a command or switch in linux - here&amp;rsquo;s two great ways to find help; all from the comfort of your terminal!
&amp;ndash;help Virtually all commands in linux have built-in help, all you need to do is append --help to the end of your command.</description></item><item><title>Week 1: OSINT Chalange Writeup</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/week1_writeup/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/week1_writeup/</guid><description><![CDATA[Intro The first-week challenge covers the basics of OSINT research, opening remote connections and password cracking. I will try to cover most of the methods we can use to get through Jack&rsquo;s cat and Ben&rsquo;s secure passwords. Without further ado, let&rsquo;s begin.
Challenge 1: Web Username The first one was very tricky for me as I am not a cat person and don&rsquo;t enjoy cat pictures&hellip; Anyway, as we go to the landing page, we can see that there are home(1) and login(2) pages and some information(3) about some employees.]]></description></item><item><title>Introduction, Recon &amp; OSINT Taster Session</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2021_taster_session/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 20:14:41 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2021_taster_session/</guid><description>Welcome back to our first official session for the new academic year, it was great to finally meet you all in real life. This is a quick recap of what we did.
What is ComSec? Welcome to ComSec, we are Coventry University&amp;rsquo;s Ethical Hacking Society. We aim to share our knowledge around cybersecurity and to create a strong info-sec community. Our aims:
Teach cybersecurity Organise talks with businesses Organise university wide competitions Compete internationally with our team ‘Ethical Slackers Committee 2021 This year the committee is:</description></item><item><title>We're Back!</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/welcome_2021/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/welcome_2021/</guid><description>Welcome to a new year at ComSec — Coventry University&amp;rsquo;s unofficial ethical hacking society. We are proud to announce due to the relaxation of COVID-19 rules, we will be holding in-person events every week on Wednesday at 2pm. Also, if the interest is there; we will offer a live-streamed version available on our Discord channel (please let the committee know prior to the session). We would also, like to take this opportunity to formally welcome our latest committee member, Ben!</description></item></channel></rss>