<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on CUEH ComSec</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on CUEH ComSec</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 12:40:28 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to Contribute</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/contributing/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 May 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/contributing/</guid><description>If you are a member of ComSec, we would love you to contribute to our site; and as a reward we will display your name as the article&amp;rsquo;s author.
The type of articles we would like is anything hacking related; this could be from discussing a topic to a walkthrough to a CTF challenge.
Getting Started Firstly you will need to fork this repository. This can be done through GitHub by visiting our repository and by clicking fork in the top right corner.</description></item><item><title>Welcome!</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/welcome/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 23:14:41 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/welcome/</guid><description>Welcome to the new website for ComSec! We hope you find it to be an improvement to the last, as we feel the new layout will make our content easier to reach.
Main Improvements The main improvements to the site are:
dark theme post tagging clear author We also wish to encourage more users to post content (such as walk-throughs) and they will receive full credit. I will include more information on how to contribute in the near future.</description></item><item><title>CUEHack</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/cuehack/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Mar 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/cuehack/</guid><description>To end this academic year, ComSec helped second-year student Alex to run a CTF building inspired hackathon over the weekend of the 20th of March 2021.
The idea was simple, teams had to build a CTF challenge utilising a docker template that we created as a starting point. To find out more information click here.
Entries 1st Place Ben&amp;rsquo;s Team with Viral Breakout 2nd Place Richie&amp;rsquo;s Team</description></item><item><title>Nettitude Event</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/nettitude/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/nettitude/</guid><description>Today, we will have a talk from cybersecurity business Nettitude. Topics that will be covered will be what the industry is like and their graduate/internship schemes.
You will be able to talk to graduate students and their experiences, and the event will be rounded up with a CTF competition!
To find out more about Nettitude click here.</description></item><item><title>Bulletproof Event</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/bulletproof/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/bulletproof/</guid><description>Today, we will be having a talk by cybersecurity business Bulletproof.
The talk will include topics like what it is like to work in the security industry and the many different areas. Additionally, you will be able to talk to graduate students and have a chance to ask questions. Finally, the event will be capped off with a CTF!
We would like to thank Bulletproof for holding the event, click here to find more about them.</description></item><item><title>Bug Reporting &amp; Meterpreter</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/bugreporting_meterpreter/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/bugreporting_meterpreter/</guid><description>This week we will continue from the Metasploit session and explore Meterpreter, but firstly we will look at bug reporting.
Resources Presentation Slides Bug Reporting Due to the current working at home predicament, it can be hard for lecturers and us to debug issues. Unfortunately receiving messages containing &amp;lsquo;it doesn&amp;rsquo;t work&amp;rsquo; is unhelpful and time wasting. Therefore, in this session we will cover how to bug report.
Tip Remember, before asking for help to attempt to try and solve the problem yourself (such as reading documentation, trying our top 5 mistakes and Ducking for answers).</description></item><item><title>12 Days of Christmas CTF Review</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/12days_xmas_ctf_review/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/12days_xmas_ctf_review/</guid><description>This week we will discuss solutions to the 12 days of Christmas CTF that we created. Not had a go - look at CTFd to take part!
Before starting this week, we would like to announce the winners:
1st ¯_(ツ)_/¯ 3230pts 2nd NotSuspicious 1730pts 3rd Jeff 1040pts Best Write-up - Ben We would also like to thank everyone who took part, and we hoped that you enjoyed the challenges.</description></item><item><title>Metasploit</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/metasploit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/metasploit/</guid><description>Today, we will look at Metasploit; a widely used pen testing framework. Metasploit is a massive product and today we will focus on:
What is Metasploit? What is msfconsole? What is Metasploitable2? Using Nmap in msfconsole Running an exploit using Metasploit Resources Presentation Slides Tip In the examples, I run exploits against Metasploitable 2 (a deliberately vulnerable VM). You can download it here. What is Metasploit?</description></item><item><title>12 Days of Christmas CTF</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/12days_xmas_ctf/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/12days_xmas_ctf/</guid><description>Dear Loyal Subjects,
The Three Kings have received a prophecy about the birth of God&amp;rsquo;s son in twelve days’ time!
Unfortunately, King Herald has also heard this news and has ordered the death of all babies within his kingdom. Since King Herald has many spies, we have had to enclose hidden information within this letter.
Can you help the three Kings reach God&amp;rsquo;s son and ensure his safety? To do this, each day there will be three daily challenges to complete for the next 12 days (starting 26th December) with varying difficulties aimed at a range of abilities.</description></item><item><title>Guest - 0verfl0w_ - Banking Malware</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/bankingmalware_overfl0w/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Dec 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/bankingmalware_overfl0w/</guid><description>This week we had a talk by a second-year student, 0verfl0w_ about banking malware and his experience while working as a Principal Security Analyst. Additionally, he has developed a Beginner Malware Analysis Course, Zero2Automated, and worked with SentinelOne to develop free online training courses.
Here is a copy of the presentation. If you have any questions, feel free to reach out to @0verfl0w_ on Twitter.</description></item><item><title>CrowdStrike Event</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/crowdstrike_event/</link><pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/crowdstrike_event/</guid><description>Our university has been hacked!!!! CrowdStrike and ComSec request your help in identifying the malicious attackers. Can you help us identify the attackers before Warwick, Southampton and Edinburgh Napier do?
This week we will complete a blue team, security operation centre type challenge!
Unfortunately, places are limited this week, and require booking in advance - to book, view our post on either Aula or Discord
Who are CrowdStrike? &amp;lsquo;CrowdStrike was founded in 2011 to fix a fundamental problem: The sophisticated attacks that were forcing the world’s leading businesses into the headlines could not be solved with existing malware-based defences.</description></item><item><title>Guest - ROP Chains</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/sleepunderflow_rop/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/sleepunderflow_rop/</guid><description>This week, we had a talk by graduate student and security consultant at Nettitude, Sleepunderflow! To view the materials he used, head to his GitHub Repo
Resources Presentation Slides Live Session Recording</description></item><item><title>Guest Lecturer - Buffer Overflows</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/dan_buffer_overflow/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Nov 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/dan_buffer_overflow/</guid><description>This week we had a guest lecture by Dan, a senior lecturer at Coventry University. To view his materials and challenges, please visit Coventry University GitHub.</description></item><item><title>OSINT &amp; Social Engineering</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/osint_social_engineering/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/osint_social_engineering/</guid><description>This week, I gave an introductory talk on open-source intelligence (OSINT) and social engineering. We also delved into the theories of why social engineering can be a successful attack and why humans are vulnerable to it!
Resources Presentation Slides OSINT Open-Source Intelligence is the art of finding information from publicly available sources. This is crucial in pen testing (as the more you know about the company you are hacking – the easier it can become).</description></item><item><title>Web Exploitation &amp; OWASP</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/owasp_sqli_xss/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Nov 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/owasp_sqli_xss/</guid><description>This week we will begin to look at website exploitation, using the OWASP top 10. The main areas we will cover are:
Good notes, and their importance Making notes with Markdown What is website exploitation? Introduction to OWASP top 10 SQL Injection Sqlmap Cross-Site Scripting (XSS) Sensitive Data Exposure Resources Presentation Slides Note Taking Effective hacking requires a thorough and methodological approach. Additionally, in the workplace you will have to report findings to clients and be able to work with others.</description></item><item><title>Graduate Talks - Ziemni</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/ziemni/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/ziemni/</guid><description>This week we had a presentation by a graduate student, Ziemni. He is currently studying for a Masters in Cybersecurity Management &amp;amp; is frequently in the HackTheBox top 10. He details how he has improved himself throughout his time at Coventry University &amp;amp; the importance of practising hacking.
The main talking points were:
Ziemni&amp;rsquo;s background Where to start/background Importance of CTFs &amp;amp; Practice Different CTF programs Live HTB demo Resources Here are the resources used:</description></item><item><title>Web Enumeration Writeup</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/web_enum_writeup/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/web_enum_writeup/</guid><description>Web Enumeration ctf Start your docker instances and let&amp;rsquo;s hack! 8 flags inside this machine
Every time first thing to do Nmap scan Look at your scan results. So we have one port open 3838/tcp and we have at least one directory &amp;lsquo;/legal&amp;rsquo; and one file robots.txt and the box is running nginx. First thing lets open the browser and navigate to 172.17.0.2 Get a good look at the source code and the style.</description></item><item><title>Web Enumeration</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/web_enum/</link><pubDate>Thu, 22 Oct 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/web_enum/</guid><description>In this session, we will look at website enumeration and exploitation. This is what we will cover in further detail:
What is Enumeration? Directory Brute Forcing Checking Comments &amp;amp; Common Files Directory Traversal Google Dorking (basics) Server Fingerprinting &amp;amp; Other Tools Web Shells Resources Presentation Slides Live Session Recording What is Enumeration? Enumeration is the process of going through a list, one by one, to find information.</description></item><item><title>ComSec Introduction Writeup</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/welcome_nmap_writeup/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/welcome_nmap_writeup/</guid><description>Nmap 1 So first week of comsec I hope everyone enjoyed the slides and is prepared for the ctf.
after running this commands
1 2 3 git clone https://github.com/Cov-ComSec/ComSecMaterials.git cd docker1 docker-compose up After running this commands you should see something like this in your terminal.
If you do see this it means you are ready for playing. Minimize your shell open a new one and start scanning.</description></item><item><title>How-To: docker-compose</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/docker-compose/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/docker-compose/</guid><description>This year we will be using a lot of docker machines. They are like virtual machines, however slimed down, therefore using less resources and have smaller file sizes. We recommend running docker on your Kali Linux machine (or Debian based distribution), even though it can run on Windows, it can be temperamental at times. Therefore, this is a guide for Linux only.
Installation Firstly, ensure your system is fully up to date, then install the necessary packages.</description></item><item><title>Installing Kali Linux on VMware</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/vm_setup/</link><pubDate>Sat, 17 Oct 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/vm_setup/</guid><description>In this short guide I will show you how to install Kali Linux, using VMware Workstation Pro (which is provided free to Coventry University students) on Windows 10.
Downloading VMware As mentioned above, if you are a Coventry University Student, you are able to install VMware Pro for free. To grab your product key, you must head to this site and login using your university credentials. Once signed in go to Students -&amp;gt; Development Tools -&amp;gt; VMware and choose the latest version of VMware Workstation pro and follow the standard instructions.</description></item><item><title>ComSec Introduction</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/welcome_nmap/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Oct 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/welcome_nmap/</guid><description>This week is the first session of the academic year, and we will cover:
What is ComSec? Network Scanning with Nmap Introduction to TryHackMe Resources Presentation Slides Live Session Recording Docker-Compose Challenges Challenge 1 Challenge 2 What is ComSec? Firstly, welcome to ComSec, we are the university&amp;rsquo;s unofficial ethical hacking society. This year the club will be led by second year students Jack Orcherton, Martin Schon and Tiago Pascoal.</description></item></channel></rss>