<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>CTF - Tag - CUEH ComSec</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/tags/ctf/</link><description>CTF - Tag - CUEH ComSec</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 22:40:28 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cov-comsec.github.io/tags/ctf/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Week 2: Scanning and Enumeration</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/scanning/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 22:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/scanning/</guid><description>In this session we will begin to look at scanning and enummeration, and start to look at some of the associated tools.
Warm Up - Getting help in the Terminal Ever forgotten a command or switch in linux - here&amp;rsquo;s two great ways to find help; all from the comfort of your terminal!
&amp;ndash;help Virtually all commands in linux have built-in help, all you need to do is append --help to the end of your command.</description></item><item><title>12 Days of Christmas CTF Review</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/12days_xmas_ctf_review/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/12days_xmas_ctf_review/</guid><description>This week we will discuss solutions to the 12 days of Christmas CTF that we created. Not had a go - look at CTFd to take part!
Before starting this week, we would like to announce the winners:
1st ¯_(ツ)_/¯ 3230pts 2nd NotSuspicious 1730pts 3rd Jeff 1040pts Best Write-up - Ben We would also like to thank everyone who took part, and we hoped that you enjoyed the challenges.</description></item><item><title>12 Days of Christmas CTF</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/12days_xmas_ctf/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/12days_xmas_ctf/</guid><description>Dear Loyal Subjects,
The Three Kings have received a prophecy about the birth of God&amp;rsquo;s son in twelve days’ time!
Unfortunately, King Herald has also heard this news and has ordered the death of all babies within his kingdom. Since King Herald has many spies, we have had to enclose hidden information within this letter.
Can you help the three Kings reach God&amp;rsquo;s son and ensure his safety? To do this, each day there will be three daily challenges to complete for the next 12 days (starting 26th December) with varying difficulties aimed at a range of abilities.</description></item></channel></rss>