<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Metasploit - Tag - CUEH ComSec</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/tags/metasploit/</link><description>Metasploit - Tag - CUEH ComSec</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 12:40:28 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cov-comsec.github.io/tags/metasploit/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Week 1: OSINT Chalange Writeup</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/week1_writeup/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/week1_writeup/</guid><description><![CDATA[Intro The first-week challenge covers the basics of OSINT research, opening remote connections and password cracking. I will try to cover most of the methods we can use to get through Jack&rsquo;s cat and Ben&rsquo;s secure passwords. Without further ado, let&rsquo;s begin.
Challenge 1: Web Username The first one was very tricky for me as I am not a cat person and don&rsquo;t enjoy cat pictures&hellip; Anyway, as we go to the landing page, we can see that there are home(1) and login(2) pages and some information(3) about some employees.]]></description></item><item><title>Bug Reporting &amp; Meterpreter</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/bugreporting_meterpreter/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/bugreporting_meterpreter/</guid><description>This week we will continue from the Metasploit session and explore Meterpreter, but firstly we will look at bug reporting.
Resources Presentation Slides Bug Reporting Due to the current working at home predicament, it can be hard for lecturers and us to debug issues. Unfortunately receiving messages containing &amp;lsquo;it doesn&amp;rsquo;t work&amp;rsquo; is unhelpful and time wasting. Therefore, in this session we will cover how to bug report.
Tip Remember, before asking for help to attempt to try and solve the problem yourself (such as reading documentation, trying our top 5 mistakes and Ducking for answers).</description></item><item><title>Metasploit</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/metasploit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/metasploit/</guid><description>Today, we will look at Metasploit; a widely used pen testing framework. Metasploit is a massive product and today we will focus on:
What is Metasploit? What is msfconsole? What is Metasploitable2? Using Nmap in msfconsole Running an exploit using Metasploit Resources Presentation Slides Tip In the examples, I run exploits against Metasploitable 2 (a deliberately vulnerable VM). You can download it here. What is Metasploit?</description></item></channel></rss>