<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>writeup - Tag - CUEH ComSec</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/tags/writeup/</link><description>writeup - Tag - CUEH ComSec</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 12:40:28 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://cov-comsec.github.io/tags/writeup/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Writeup: Hack The Box Cyber Apocalypse 2023 - The Cursed Mission</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2023_hackthebox_cyberapoc/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/2023_hackthebox_cyberapoc/</guid><description>The HackTheBox Cyber Apocalypse has become a staple annual event of the ComSec CTF calendar, though this year a couple of changed were introduced - such as the maximum team size and average difficulty of the challenges. This post contains some challenges
Contents
Contents
rev: Alien Saboteur Understanding the VM Reversing the VM Program - bin Getting the First Password Unravelling more Code Finding the Flag pwn: Control Room Configure Engine Exploitation rev: Alien Saboteur Solved by Ben R, this was rated a medium difficulty challenge, and his personal favourite challenge in the CTF.</description></item><item><title>DownUnder CTF 2022</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/down-under-ctf-2022/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2022 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/down-under-ctf-2022/</guid><description>DownUnder CTF was a 48 hour CTF that began on Friday 23rd September 2022. It was the first CTF of the year that ComSec played, we had quite a few new members playing this one so it was a great chance for them to practice their skills.
This article contains writeups of a range of difficulty and category, so this should be a good place for new members to see what a jeopardy style CTF looks like.</description></item><item><title>Web Enumeration Writeup</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/web_enum_writeup/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/web_enum_writeup/</guid><description>Web Enumeration ctf Start your docker instances and let&amp;rsquo;s hack! 8 flags inside this machine
Every time first thing to do Nmap scan Look at your scan results. So we have one port open 3838/tcp and we have at least one directory &amp;lsquo;/legal&amp;rsquo; and one file robots.txt and the box is running nginx. First thing lets open the browser and navigate to 172.17.0.2 Get a good look at the source code and the style.</description></item><item><title>ComSec Introduction Writeup</title><link>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/welcome_nmap_writeup/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2020 12:40:28 +0100</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/welcome_nmap_writeup/</guid><description>Nmap 1 Welcome to ComSec&amp;rsquo;s first challenge! This week we will be targeting a docker container, to start it, issue the following two commands:
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 $ wget https://cov-comsec.github.io/posts/welcome_nmap/c1/docker-compose.yaml $ sudo docker-compose up [sudo] password for kali: WARNING: Found orphan containers (kali_evilweb_1) for this project. If you removed or renamed this service in your compose file, you can run this command with the --remove-orphans flag to clean it up.</description></item></channel></rss>